Interviewer: What do you do, Ollie?
Ollie: I work in digital marketing, I do the social media for different companies on Facebook, Instagram, and Google.
Interviewer: What about Andrew? What does he do?
Ollie: He works for a publishing company. He’s an editor.
Interviewer: Where in the house do you work?
Ollie: I work at the kitchen table most of the time.
Andrew’s in the office two days a week, but normally he sits opposite me. We live in a very small flat!
Interviewer: Do you work long hours?
Ollie: Not really. I start at about 10.00, when I get back from the gym, and I finish at about 6.00.
Interviewer: And Andrew? Does he work long hours?
Ollie: He also works from 10.00 until 6.00, but sometimes he works in the evenings when he’s really busy.
Interviewer: What do you think are the pros and cons of working from home?
Ollie: The good thing is that I don’t need to travel to work. That’s fantastic. And we have lunch together.
The bad thing is that sometimes we need to make phone calls or have meetings,
so one of us needs to go to the bedroom, and it’s a very small bedroom.
And I miss chatting to people at work, and going to the pub with them after work.
Interviewer: Do you have tips for other people who work from home together?
Ollie: Tell the other person when you have meetings or phone calls.
Work in another space for some of the week, if possible.
Don’t sit in the same place all day – stand up and move, make coffee.
Stop work for lunch, and turn off your computer. And it helps if you like the same music!